Guide to the Richard Foreman and Kate Manheim Papers MSS.152
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIV: Media
  - Subseries B: Sound Effects - Originals
    - Title: Drum catch (Box 1P, Folder ID: 152.1144)
    - Title: Zor Whistle (A: Sex F) (Box 1P, Folder ID: 152.1145)
    - Title: Org Scale / Sunny 2 (Box 1P, Folder ID: 152.1146)
    - Title: Stk: Beats Dm. (Box 1P, Folder ID: 152.1147)
    - Title: Dub A (Box 1P, Folder ID: 152.1148)
    - Title: RM Dialog (Box 1P, Folder ID: 152.1149)
    - Title: Deamons / Tone (Box 1P, Folder ID: 152.1150)
    - Title: WaWa / Synco Bt (Box 1P, Folder ID: 152.1151)
    - Title: Ask (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1152)
    - Title: P. Rocking (A: Dan 16) (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1153)
    - Title: Nurses / Trill (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1154)
    - Title: Zap (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1155)
    - Title: Clock / Blast (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1156)
    - Title: Cornfield (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1157)
    - Title: [Ripa?] / Number (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1158)
      Tape Brand: Metal Position Type IV MA-XG
    - Title: Org. Oss / Slo Gong (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1159)
    - Title: Calm / Forge (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1160)
    - Title: Loopy (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1161)
    - Title: Wiel / Drum 2 12 (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1162)
    - Title: Poesy (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1163)
    - Title: Slo's (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1164)
    - Title: Epic / Clock #12 (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1165)
    - Title: Pretend (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1166)
    - Title: H Zero (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1167)
    - Title: Slap / Whine (B: Waller) (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1168)
    - Title: Drag (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1169)
    - Title: Trickle (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1170)
    - Title: Turando / Goof (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1171)
    - Title: Rota Blare (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1172)
    - Title: Drum Rif (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1173)
    - Title: Tremor (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1174)
    - Title: Drums 1-2 (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1175)
    - Title: Checko (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1176)
    - Title: Piano Trill (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1177)
    - Title: Dan 16 / Flutter (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1178)
    - Title: Mellow (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1179)
    - Title: Nuts (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1180)
    - Title: Hi Sop / Sop Round (A: Sunday Papers / Tap 1) (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1181)
    - Title: Violin Sob / Monro Org (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1182)
    - Title: Rocking / Drum (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1183)
    - Title: Tone (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1184)
    - Title: Lo - Lotsy (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1185)
    - Title: Ringtone (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1186)
    - Title: Choir / C. Porter (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1187)
    - Title: H Zip (A: Hulla Blues) (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1188)
    - Title: School (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1189)
    - Title: Blare Rhym (M) (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1190)
    - Title: Drip (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1191)
    - Title: Yowl (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1192)
    - Title: Toy (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1193)
    - Title: Violin Tred (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1194)
    - Title: Nursery Flute (A: Chug - Chug - Slow) (B: LAF / DADJ.) (Box 1P.a, Folder ID: 152.1195)
    - Title: Clock (A: Bach P - Pip) (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1196)
      Tape Brand: Sony Type I (Normal) Bias HF-S
    - Title: Sustain Mes (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1197)
    - Title: Stk: Main Brf (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1198)
    - Title: Sop - Dala (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1199)
    - Title: Church / Sheep (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1200)
    - Title: Sop Latin / Honk (B: Loops 1-4 1/16/84) (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1201)
    - Title: Lovely / ChaCha (A: D. Cord / [___]-S-Saw) (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1202)
    - Title: Tinkle (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1203)
    - Title: Tremelo Slo (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1204)
    - Title: Better Than Love (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1205)
    - Title: Plops (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1206)
    - Title: Banjo Rpt. (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1207)
    - Title: Rota Umph (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1208)
    - Title: Discover (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1209)
    - Title: Chug - Organ (B: Bis) (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1210)
    - Title: Rota hopla (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1211)
    - Title: Rota Pump (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1212)
    - Title: Ziplina (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1213)
    - Title: Violin (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1214)
    - Title: Soft (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1215)
    - Title: Baroom (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1216)
    - Title: Org Slo / Piano Scale (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1217)
    - Title: Raygun (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1218)
    - Title: Key Mid (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1219)
    - Title: Breath (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1220)
    - Title: Sop haha (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1221)
    - Title: Note (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1222)
    - Title: Drum Gun / Radio (A: M. Xylo / Thud) (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1223)
    - Title: V. Circle (M) (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1224)
    - Title: Hapy (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1225)
    - Title: Ubrn / Jazz (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1226)
    - Title: Moan (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1227)
    - Title: G - gong (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1228)
    - Title: G. Chimes (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1229)
    - Title: Latin gersh (A: Salsa Strum) (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1230)
    - Title: Rat Tat (Latino) (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1231)
    - Title: G. Flair (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1232)
    - Title: V Slo / Tone (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1233)
    - Title: Serio / Menace (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1234)
    - Title: Quiver (A: String) (Box 1Q, Folder ID: 152.1235)
    - Title: Lab: Menace (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1236)
    - Title: Rapid Thuds (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1237)
    - Title: Rink Org / Gong (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1238)
    - Title: Passive Viol (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1239)
    - Title: Bell / Gong (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1240)
    - Title: E: Placid (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1241)
    - Title: March Osil (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1242)
      Tape Brand: Sony UX-ES
    - Title: Pling Waltz (L) (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1243)
    - Title: Dub 10 (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1244)
    - Title: Eddie B. (A: G. chord) (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1245)
      Performance: Eddie Goes to Poetry City [?]
    - Title: Creole / Pump Chaw (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1246)
    - Title: Warp (A: Bag of tricks) (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1247)
    - Title: Heaven D. / L: Smooth (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1248)
    - Title: Harpsi / Thmptmt (B: Org Hollow / China Eau) (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1249)
    - Title: Latino (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1250)
    - Title: Muffled (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1251)
    - Title: Osil - Saw (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1252)
    - Title: Hit / Locust (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1253)
    - Title: Wheez Stk (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1254)
    - Title: Voice (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1255)
    - Title: Drm Bts (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1256)
    - Title: Gong / Sop. Insist (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1257)
    - Title: Org Mick (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1258)
    - Title: Flutter Z / Hip drum (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1259)
    - Title: Org (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1260)
    - Title: Hit (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1261)
    - Title: Violin Whine (A: Drum) (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1262)
    - Title: Fast Drum / Org. Klee 32 (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1263)
      Duration: 48 minutes
    - Title: Saw (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1264)
    - Title: Eno (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1265)
    - Title: P'no Ripple (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1266)
    - Title: Felini / Dance Broken (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1267)
    - Title: Drum Down (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1268)
    - Title: Choral 2 CT (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1269)
    - Title: Hora / Bell 13 (B: Free Jazz) (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1270)
    - Title: grate (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1271)
    - Title: China BT (A: A-No) (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1272)
    - Title: Break (L) (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1273)
    - Title: V. Chaw (Box 1Q.a, Folder ID: 152.1274)
    - Title: Bach Unit (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1275)
    - Title: Matin / Sheep (A: Long Film 1) (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1276)
    - Title: Clump / Whine (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1277)
    - Title: Monro Xylo / Rattat (A: Pluckyo / Hip Drum) (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1278)
    - Title: Monk Zip (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1279)
    - Title: Pace (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1280)
    - Title: 6) Tone / Trill (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1281)
    - Title: Keys: Mesan (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1282)
    - Title: Boys R (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1283)
    - Title: 8) Mellow / Slo (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1284)
    - Title: 14) Rota X / Bach Org (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1285)
    - Title: How much (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1286)
    - Title: Bird call (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1287)
    - Title: Rhyh. Bell A (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1288)
    - Title: 16) Piano (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1289)
    - Title: Geson (B: Beautiful / Jungle) (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1290)
    - Title: Rota Squeze (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1291)
    - Title: 1-2-3 (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1292)
    - Title: 10) Table Manners (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1293)
    - Title: Chinese gong (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1294)
    - Title: Hulot (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1295)
    - Title: Big Walk / Thud 27 (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1296)
    - Title: Conga (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1297)
    - Title: Rock / L. Gersh (A: Piano hip / Zoar Whirl) (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1298)
    - Title: Sunny / Geeson (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1299)
    - Title: Mass / Tribe (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1300)
    - Title: Space Warp / A / B / Song (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1301)
    - Title: Train / China (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1302)
    - Title: Giggle / Stormy W. 22 (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1303)
    - Title: Org: Steam (A: L. Lunch) (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1304)
    - Title: Bang Dang (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1305)
    - Title: Sop Bang (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1306)
    - Title: SWQ (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1307)
    - Title: Rinky CT (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1308)
    - Title: E: Mellow (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1309)
    - Title: G. Return (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1310)
    - Title: G: Waves (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1311)
    - Title: Da Bells / by Da Free John / © 1982 The Johannine Daist Communion (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1312)
    - Title: Sop (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1313)
    - Title: Org 3D (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1314)
    - Title: V. Circle (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1315)
    - Title: Chugs (Box 1R, Folder ID: 152.1316)
    - Title: Screetch (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1317)
    - Title: 4) Repete / Jog (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1318)
    - Title: Slo Quirk (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1319)
    - Title: F. Strum (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1320)
    - Title: Piano Trill (M) (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1321)
    - Title: Viol. Nudge (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1322)
    - Title: V round (M) (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1323)
    - Title: Bach 178 (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1324)
    - Title: Pre(FLM B / "0" (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1325)
    - Title: 3. Chug / Rota Whirl (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1326)
    - Title: P Quiver (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1327)
    - Title: 10) Bop / Nite (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1328)
    - Title: Ride Vamp (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1329)
    - Title: Heavy / Burble (B: Base Bal / Bambo) (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1330)
    - Title: Flam (A) / Flm (C) (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1331)
    - Title: Kreisler / Schumann (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1332)
    - Title: Slow deep / Cramp 1 (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1333)
    - Title: E: Mello 2 (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1334)
    - Title: Rap (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1335)
    - Title: Dum Dum (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1336)
    - Title: Idle / Loll, cuid34712 (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1337)
    - Title: D Sad (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1338)
    - Title: Drum (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1339)
    - Title: Horn Slap / Horn (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1340)
    - Title: 13) accord / xylo (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1341)
    - Title: Tone / Stock Main (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1342)
    - Title: Monk idle (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1343)
    - Title: #52 Held Hitch (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1344)
    - Title: Vigor (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1345)
    - Title: H Frantic / Wiz Bang (A: Indian Fire) (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1346)
    - Title: Bla Synco / Tomt (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1347)
    - Title: Massenet (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1348)
    - Title: Gunch CT (A: copy) (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1349)
    - Title: 12) Monk / Busy (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1350)
    - Title: Hip (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1351)
    - Title: Import / Sweet V (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1352)
    - Title: Melody CT (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1353)
    - Title: Strum CT (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1354)
    - Title: Chimes - CT (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1355)
    - Title: Sop Quivr (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1356)
    - Title: Sop Hi / Yid Strum 9 (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1357)
    - Title: Plinky CT (Box 1R.a, Folder ID: 152.1358)
    - Title: Flem (B) / Drum (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1359)
    - Title: Helene (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1360)
    - Title: Time Maids (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1361)
    - Title: Burp 3B (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1362)
    - Title: Sky Desert (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1363)
    - Title: G. Rise (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1364)
    - Title: E: Strum (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1365)
    - Title: Dan 15 / Claude (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1366)
    - Title: Ripples CT (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1367)
    - Title: Chorus / Rota Umph (B: Sex E / Twang) (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1368)
    - Title: Scretch (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1369)
    - Title: Slo Stroke / Wistful (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1370)
    - Title: Waller / Oseil Saw (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1371)
    - Title: Play 1 / You Can Do (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1372)
    - Title: Big Walk (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1373)
    - Title: Johnson / Paddle Org (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1374)
    - Title: Swt / Blksmith (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1375)
    - Title: Wheeze / Tex Loop (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1376)
    - Title: Gong / Bell 24 (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1377)
    - Title: Hindu / Choros 7 (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1378)
    - Title: Tap 1 / Tap 2 (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1379)
    - Title: Salsa B / Salsa Strum (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1380)
    - Title: L Cut / Dead Cord (A: Don 3) (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1381)
    - Title: Bach V-Saw (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1382)
    - Title: Heavy (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1383)
    - Title: Saw / Boom (A: D-G Pump) (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1384)
    - Title: Monro. Org / M. S. Saw (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1385)
    - Title: Desert / Piano (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1386)
    - Title: Roses / Lite (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1387)
    - Title: Sweet / Blacksmith 20 (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1388)
    - Title: Space Warp / Org Wp. (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1389)
    - Title: Saw (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1390)
    - Title: King / Idle (B: Masters), cuid34713 (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1391)
      Duration: 116 minutes
    - Title: Soft X / Heavy (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1392)
    - Title: Massenet / Ave. Mar. (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1393)
    - Title: E: Lake (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1394)
    - Title: Geson / Monk Idle (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1395)
    - Title: Mellow / Cheep (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1396)
    - Title: E: Classic (Box 1S, Folder ID: 152.1397)
    - Title: Sft. Ring (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1398)
    - Title: Seem-Saw (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1399)
    - Title: E. Elegant (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1400)
    - Title: Bt. Mole (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1401)
    - Title: Knock Rhm. (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1402)
    - Title: Harpsi / Thmpthmp (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1403)
    - Title: Sop Hit / Dub 7 (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1404)
    - Title: G. Wist (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1405)
    - Title: Hollow / Piano (B: Party 2 / Party C) (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1406)
    - Title: Choral CT (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1407)
    - Title: Piano 1B (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1408)
    - Title: Org. Hollow (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1409)
    - Title: Rota Perk (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1410)
    - Title: E: Psalm (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1411)
    - Title: Ode (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1412)
    - Title: Calm (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1413)
    - Title: Slo Moan (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1414)
    - Title: Violin X (B: Honk / Break) (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1415)
    - Title: Harbor (A: Dan Rag) (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1416)
    - Title: Soft X / Chorus (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1417)
    - Title: H. Gangle (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1418)
    - Title: Mellow B / Hi Sop (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1419)
    - Title: B. Train (A: Falsetto / Romantic) (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1420)
    - Title: Zips / Xcentro (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1421)
    - Title: Hi Sop / Tap City (A: Slo Disco Pluck / Soft) (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1422)
    - Title: Weird W / Syntha (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1423)
    - Title: Plings (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1424)
    - Title: Tone / Alpha (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1425)
    - Title: V. Round (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1426)
    - Title: G - idle (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1427)
    - Title: Whiz Bang / P. Just (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1428)
    - Title: Wistf / Lovely (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1429)
    - Title: Hi Sop / Jolly (B: Honk) (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1430)
    - Title: Alpha / Org SA = Clear No Bass (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1431)
    - Title: Bells / Ominous (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1432)
    - Title: Calm / Mon Xylo (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1433)
    - Title: Heavy / Mellow (A: Welch Slo / Bagpipe) (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1434)
    - Title: P. Yearn / Wiz Bang (Box 1S.a, Folder ID: 152.1435)
    - Title: Zine / Bloop (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1436)
      Related ID's: 152.1437-152.1449
      Related Titles: Violin Slep / Agit Base / Boom / Lite CT / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Key High / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: Violin Slep (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1437)
      Related ID's: 152.1436; 152.1438-152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Agit Base / Boom / Lite CT / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Key High / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: Agit Base (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1438)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1437; 152.1439-152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Boom / Lite CT / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Key High / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: Boom (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1439)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1438; 152.1440-152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Agit Base / Lite CT / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Key High / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: Lite CT (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1440)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1439; 152.1441-152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Agit Base / Boom / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Key High / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: G. Chug (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1441)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1440; 152.1442-152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Agit Base / Boom / Lite CT / [Untitled] / Key High / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: [Untitled] (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1442)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1441; 152.1443-152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Agit Base / Boom / Lite CT / G. Chug / Key High / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: Key High (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1443)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1442; 152.1444-152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Agit Base / Boom / Lite CT / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: Sex A Slo (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1444)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1443; 152.1445-152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Agit Base / Boom / Lite CT / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Key High / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: Oars (A: G Trip) (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1445)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1444; 152.1446-152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Agit Base / Boom / Lite CT / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Key High / Sex A Slo / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: Crystal 38 (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1446)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1445; 152.1447-152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Agit Base / Boom / Lite CT / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Key High / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: Bach Swingle (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1447)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1446; 152.1448-152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Agit Base / Boom / Lite CT / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Key High / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Rota Squeek / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: Rota Squeek (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1448)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1447; 152.1449
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Agit Base / Boom / Lite CT / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Key High / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Epoch B. Steel
    - Title: Epoch B. Steel (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1449)
      Related ID's: 152.1436-152.1448
      Related Titles: Zine/Bloop / Violin Slep / Agit Base / Boom / Lite CT / G. Chug / [Untitled] / Key High / Sex A Slo / Oars (A: G Trip) / Crystal 38 / Bach Swingle / Rota Squeek
    - Title: 11) Play / Tink (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1450)
    - Title: Weber 4 (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1451)
    - Title: Acordian (A: Bach [into ______?]) (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1452)
    - Title: Choral 1 (M) (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1453)
    - Title: Beguine (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1454)
    - Title: Soviet / Sax (A: 2Tone) (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1455)
    - Title: Vibe (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1456)
    - Title: Bop X (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1457)
    - Title: Busoni prime (A: Disco[vere?]d a line) (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1458)
    - Title: G Note (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1459)
    - Title: Zing (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1460)
    - Title: Hysteric (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1461)
    - Title: Rota X (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1462)
    - Title: Bird / Bird Brf (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1463)
    - Title: Fst bleat (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1464)
    - Title: Vibrate (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1465)
    - Title: Monk Idle / Drm Roll (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1466)
    - Title: Wood Xylo A (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1467)
    - Title: Boom Boom (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1468)
    - Title: Arab Beat (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1469)
    - Title: Choral (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1470)
    - Title: Jaz Violin (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1471)
    - Title: Idle / Flute (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1472)
    - Title: Falsetto (B: Whine / Uhuh) (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1473)
    - Title: BT Mota (A: Welsch slo) (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1474)
    - Title: P. Chinks / Runs (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1475)
    - Title: Fast Pluck (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1476)
    - Title: Yearn (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1477)
    - Title: V-lm Low (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1478)
    - Title: Dub 2 (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1479)
    - Title: Mon. Xylo / P. Joy (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1480)
    - Title: Brecht / Sop Bep (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1481)
    - Title: Crowd (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1482)
    - Title: P. Sop / Choral (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1483)
    - Title: Vib / Bop (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1484)
    - Title: Bach flute (Box 2A, Folder ID: 152.1485)
    - Title: Piano / String (Box 2A.a, Folder ID: 152.1486)
    - Title: Disco / Clarinet (Box 2A.a, Folder ID: 152.1487)
    - Title: Mumers / Don't be [Ala?] (Box 2A.a, Folder ID: 152.1488)
    - Title: Checkos / Stk. Lump (Box 2A.a, Folder ID: 152.1489)